{
  "title": "Traveling Downunder: How can I immigrate to Australia?",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Tourists who visit Australia without a visa will usually be ........ entry into the country. ",
      "answers": ["refused", "rejected", "revoked", "rebuked"],
      "correct": "refused"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "The Australian government has decided to increase the number of ........ available to skilled workers next year",
      "answers": ["passports", "documents", "visas", "passes"],
      "correct": "visas"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "The Australian minister for ........ has come under a lot of scrutiny lately for her department's decision to issue refugee status to boat people from Papua. ",
      "answers": ["immigrant", "emigrant", "colonization", "immigration"],
      "correct": "immigration"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Newly arrived migrants must live in Australia for a period of two years before they are eligible to become permanent ........",
      "answers": ["nationalities", "populations", "residents", "inhabitants"],
      "correct": "residents"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "There has been a sharp increase in the number of boat people ........ to Australia in the past ten years. ",
      "answers": ["arriving", "traveling", "departing", "transiting"],
      "correct": "traveling"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Australia is a ........ country and therefore has the right to choose whether or not tourists are granted with visas. ",
      "answers": ["independent", "governing", "autonomous", "sovereign"],
      "correct": "sovereign"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "People with a known history of tuberculosis will automatically be ........ from entering Australia. ",
      "answers": ["refused", "rejected", "discarded", "disqualified"],
      "correct": "disqualified"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Australian citizens who are receiving social security benefits from the government are not permitted to ....... tourists wanting to travel to Australia. ",
      "answers": ["benefactor", "sponsor", "giver", "donor"],
      "correct": "sponsor"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Tourists involved in illegal activities such as drug trafficking and prostitution may have their visas ....... permanently and be banned from entering Australia at any time in the futue. ",
      "answers": ["cancelled", "called off", "abandoned", "annulled"],
      "correct": "cancelled"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Retirement visas do not ........ to Australian permanent residency or citizenship. However people with this type of visa my stay in Australia for a long period of time. ",
      "answers": ["lead", "result", "generate", "develop"],
      "correct": "lead"
    }
  ]
}
